laplink.com 2016-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Laplink® Software

  * [What personal information does Laplink collect from Web site visitors?](http://www.laplink.com/index.php/en/privacy-policy#collect)

### What personal information does Laplink collect from Web site visitors?

You can freely access much of our Web site without providing any personal information. Certain areas of our Web site, such as some of our technical-support areas and the trial-software download area, require that you submit some personal information. We do not collect any personal information without your knowledge!

The type of information that we request in these online forms includes your name, address, e-mail address and company name. We also may ask you questions about the size of your organization and how you found out about our products. Not all of the information we request is required, and you may leave any of the optional questions unanswered.

### What happens to the information Laplink collects?

The information that you provide to us when you register to download free trial software or register a product is stored with a unique identifying number. The information contained in your personal profile is not provided to anyone outside of Laplink Software Inc. nor is it shared with our designated agents. All of the information you provide during e-commerce transactions is stored by our commerce partners on a secure server which encrypts all of your personal information, including your name, address and credit card number. Information disclosed to such third parties shall be governed by their corresponding privacy policies.

Laplink Software Inc. occasionally uses the information that customers provide to send announcements about new Laplink products and services.

### Why does Laplink collect information?

The information you provide helps us to improve our software products, to personalize your experience on our Web site and to provide technical support that best suits your needs. We occasionally use the information you provide to us to send you e-mail or postal mail announcements about Laplink products and services. And we may send announcements, free gifts or special offers by mail on behalf of our partners, from time to time, if we feel the mail would be relevant to your needs.

We absolutely never provide your e-mail address or telephone number to anyone outside of Laplink Software Inc. nor do we provide it to our designated agents.

### What is Laplink’s corporate security policy?

At Laplink Software Inc, we understand and respect your concerns about privacy. Our corporate security policy is so important to us that we include a policy overview in every employee's orientation. Access to our customer database is restricted to only those employees who have a specific need for access to that data to do their job. And even then, access to the customer data is password protected. Each quarter, we review and update our Web security. In addition to safeguarding the privacy of any information you give us as you visit our site, Laplink Software Inc. has entered into partnerships with other companies that care just as deeply about your privacy concerns.

Laplink Software Inc. does not handle financial transactions via the Web, so it has no need for streaming encryption products. Laplink Software Inc. works with a third party to serve as a trusted intermediary to handle e-commerce transactions with our customers. Our commerce partners handles e-commerce on a secure server which encrypts all of our customers' personal information. To learn more about how our commerce partners manages the privacy of information in conjunction with these e-commerce transactions, please see their complete privacy statement.

### Do I have the option to "opt-out" of e-mails from Laplink?

Don't want to receive e-mail or postal mail from us? We give our Web site visitors the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes that are not directly related to our Web site at the point when we ask for the information. Your MySupport profile contains a box that you check to indicate you don't want to be sent any news or product information.

Visitors who decide they no longer wish to receive our product mailings or promotional materials sent on behalf of our partners have three options for opting-out:

  * Visit [MySupport profile](http://www.laplink.com/mysupport/editcontactpreferences.asp). Click one box to opt out of receiving future promotional materials.
  * Click the opt-out link that you'll find on each promotional e-mail.
  * Mail us a short note to tell us you no longer wish to receive the promotional materials. For prompt handling of your request, remember to include your name, your full address and your e-mail address. Send your request to:  
**Laplink Software Inc.  
600 108th Avenue NE, Suite 610   
Bellevue, WA 98004  
USA**  
Phone: 425.952.6000  
Fax: 425.952.6002

Visitors to our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside party. We do this so Laplink Software Inc. visitors can make informed choices as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

### How do I update my Laplink Support Account profile?

Through the one-stop convenience of MySupport you can register Laplink products, submit and track your requests for customer support, sign up to receive e-mail notices of new product releases and special offers or "opt-out" of such mailings.

Once you've registered with us, you may update or change your personal profile at any time by visiting the [MySupport](http://www.laplink.com/mysupport/editcontactpreferences.asp) section of our Web site.

### What is Laplink’s legal disclaimer?

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

### What happens if Laplink changes the privacy policy?

We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

We may choose to change our privacy policies in the future. At the time we decide to make any changes, however, we will post those revisions on this page so our visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances -- if any -- we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what was stated at the time we collected it, we will notify you by e-mail. Laplink Software Inc. visitors will choose whether we use their specific information in a different manner than what was presented at the time they submitted that information.

### How does Laplink use "Cookies"?

A cookie is like an electronic identification card. It is a small string of code placed on your hard drive by our Web server. The cookie allows our server to identify you when you come back for another visit. A cookie is not a program. It cannot execute or carry out any operation on your computer!

The cookie benefits you in that we automatically recognize you when you come back to our Web site and that allows us to tailor the information presented to you-based on your personal needs and past interactions with our site.

Cookies also help us to better understand general visitor interests and patterns-and that means we are able to create better Web sites!

### What is Laplink’s contact information?

Please feel free to write, call or send us an e-mail message with any questions or comments you have about our privacy policies!

**Laplink Software Inc.  
600 108th Ave NE, Suite 610  
Bellevue, WA 98007  
USA**  
Phone: 425.952.6000  
Fax: 425.952.6002  

### What happens with e-mails that I send to Laplink?

We use e-mail links located on this page and throughout on our Web site to make it easier for you to contact us directly with any questions or comments.

We read and try to reply promptly to every message. In addition to responding directly to your questions or comments, we may also keep your e-mail message on file in order to use your feedback to improve our Web site and our software. Sometimes, after reviewing your comments, we may discard the e-mail message. No personal information contained within your e-mail message would be shared with any third party without your explicit permission.
